(Episode 5)
How much is it for two?
Hello,
that would be three and a half dollars.
For how long is it open?
It is open until 5 p.m.
Thank you.
It looks exactly like your painting.
Jun Seo, is that Tae Seok?
What?
Han Tae Seok.
The girl...
Are you talking about your room attendant?
It hurts.
You are such a good guy as a friend,
but what is wrong with you?
Why do you behave like this?
Why are you...
I am sorry.
But do you know how sometimes,
you get me really upset?
She was a nice girl.
If you are just playing around,
stop right now.
I'm serious.
I am serious.
It is the first time.
What are you doing?
Aren't you going to draw me?
Is this me?
It looks strange.
Don't you think so, Tae Seok?
It looks all right to me.
Choi Eun Seo?
Is it Eun Seo?
Are you Eun Seo?
Are you Jun Seo?
Are you really my brother?
Eun Seo.
The mood is quite weird.
I couldn't serve coffee to them.
How come he didn't recognize her?
He said she was his cousin.
Do you know her well?
What does she do?
Why do you care what she does?
Who is he?
I am a friend of Jun Seo
and Shin Yu Mi's first love.
I am also the boyfriend
of the girl inside.
Ji Hwan.
What is wrong with you?
He is annoying.
I have enough headaches already.
Is she really his cousin?
That's what he said.
By the way, is it true?
Do you like her?
What is going on between Jun Seo and her?
- I...
I didn't know.
If I had known you were the one
who brought my sleepwear,
and charged my cell phone at the hotel...
I didn't know, either.
Eun Seo.
How have you been?
I've been well.
Mom and my brother have treated me well.
My brother is still fighting people.
But he doesn't hit me, at least.
I heard you moved to Seoul
because of the debt your family owed.
I see...
We didn't have enough money,
but we were poor to begin with.
Despite it all, we've been doing well
helping each other out.
I was loved very much.
You know I'm clever.
I've been happy.
Have you been worried?
Have you been worried about me?
Have you been worried about me a lot?
I've been worried a lot.
Are Mom and Dad still in the U.S.?
Yes, they are doing great.
They are in the U.S. now,
but they are coming back soon.
I miss them.
I've missed you.
I've been thinking of you a lot
these days.
Maybe it was because
I was going to meet you.
It is so great to see you.
I didn't think I would meet you again.
I am so glad.
This is great.
Are they gone?
Yes, Tae Seok will give her a ride.
You should have taken her home,
rather than worry about me.
That's fine.
She was pretty and seemed kind.
Were you that happy to see her?
You even had tears in your eyes.
It was so weird.
She was very formal to me.
What time is your flight?
Do you have time for a coffee
before you leave?
Sure.
So, is he your cousin?
Yes.
What a small world.
How could you be a cousin...
of Yoon Jun Seo, of all people?
Let's start from the beginning.
We'll forget everything that happened
between us, and start again.
You and I.
Could you consider me
your brother's best friend?
By the way, I'm in trouble now.
If Jun Seo found out I had you fired,
he wouldn't let me live.
Have you told him about it?
Could you explain it to my manager?
Could you please tell her
nothing happened?
I need to get my job back at the hotel.
I don't want him to know I quit. Please?
I never ask for a favor.
I never did.
I am sorry.
Is that important to you?
Does it matter that much to you?
Please. Ms. Choi Eun Seo
did nothing wrong.
Why do you care after all this time, sir?
Nothing happened that day.
That is true.
Choi Eun Seo.
Did I fire you for the incident that day?
Do you know how many days
you've been absent without notice?
And now you brought a man here to protest?
What?
A man? Protest?
Please leave, sir.
She is a nice girl.
True, I flirted with her
to go out with her.
So what? What is the matter with that?
How could you fire someone
for having a relationship?
- Don't you date anyone?
- Stop it.
I guess no one would date you.
How have you been?
I've been doing great.
My mom and my brother treat me well.
Your brother was really mad.
I will sleep here tonight.
What happened?
Did your brother drag you
to President Kim and...
- Choi Eun Seo, come here.
- What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
- Get out of my way.
- Jong Chul.
- Stop there.
Get over here.
Jong Chul.
Do you have any idea
what kind of a meeting it was?
How could you run away with a guy?
Jong Chul.
Do you know what you have done to me?
I can't be on a fishing boat anymore.
So, what can I do now?
Jong Chul.
You are a bad man.
What are you? Get out of my face.
What kind of a man are you?
You're terrible.
- Get out of my way.
- Jong Chul.
You jerk.
What are you going to do now?
What will you do?
- Jong Chul.
- You...
- Jong Chul, please.
- Just drop dead here.
You just drop dead.
Just die.
You just die.
You just die now.
All right, let's die together.
- Die, you bastard!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
You and I will die together.
I won't just sit still.
Wait and see what I would do to you.
- Jong Chul.
- Mom.
Jong Chul.
Where can you go?
Don't worry, mom!
I have a lot of friends.
What are you going to do
if Jong Chul comes to bother you?
You don't need to worry about me.
Mom, you take this.
Don't give it to Jong Chul.
You will have bruises
on your face tomorrow.
Jong Chul is coming.
Go now. Hurry.
Go before he beats you to death.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Did you get up early?
Did I come too early?
But, you...
I told my family about you.
They told me to stay here for a few days
since it has been so long.
Can I stay here with you for a few days?
Do you have extra space for me?
Did you run away from home?
No.
I guess I made you worry.
I didn't mean to do that.
I will go.
No, it is all right.
Then, can I stay?
Of course.
Come on in.
My brother is still fighting people.
But he doesn't hit me, at least.
- Jun Seo.
- Yes.
I...
actually ran away from home.
I had a fight with my brother.
I am sorry that I lied.
I just thought of you. So...
It is okay. You don't need to tell me.
Stay with me, okay?
I want to stay with you, Eun Seo.
I am looking forward to it.
I will stay for just a few days.
Good night, Eun Seo.
Saying good night...
and good morning,
those are the things
I wanted to say the most.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
I am sorry.
I am so sorry, Eun Seo.
Are you Mr. Choi Jong Chul?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
I am Yoon Jun Seo.
Tell your mother Eun Seo is with me.
You.
Could you be...?
If you ever touch Eun Seo again,
you will be sorry.
What did you buy so much?
I will cook for you.
We will celebrate your first class.
By the way, Eun Seo,
how do we explain to people about us?
You told them we're cousins. I like that.
Your fiancée doesn't even know about me.
So, you have kept things
a secret from her, right?
I...
It's fine. I'm not sure
how Sin Ae would take this.
Let's discuss it when
Mom and Dad are here.
Yes.
Eun Seo,
why are you speaking to me
in a formal way?
I feel a little awkward
because it's been a long time.
Did I speak to you casually before?
How is Sin Ae?
She is well.
She is tough and ambitious.
I think that's why she excelled at school.
When she gets her MBA next month,
she will come to Korea.
I see.
What is an MBA?
She was majoring in business.
It is a master's degree
in business administration, I mean...
It is a sort of certificate of business.
I see.
Tonight's dinner will be great.
I am a good cook.
You can see how good I am.
Jun Seo.
Hello.
Mom packed many different kinds of food.
Help yourself, Eun Seo.
You could've called me.
I wanted to surprise you.
Did you come to spend time with him?
How long are you staying?
I am staying for a few days.
No.
I will let her stay for a while.
Jun Seo.
Finally, you addressed me
like you would a brother.
She has nowhere to stay at the moment.
That is nice, Eun Seo.
I was concerned about
how he takes care of himself,
such as having meals and everything.
Please look after him.
Did you make this kimchi, Eun Seo?
Yes.
She likes it, and wants to learn
how to make it.
You could've told me
you're staying with Eun Seo.
I was embarrassed.
It wasn't planned.
Are you annoyed?
No, if you are with your sister,
I would be relieved.
Also, you can't cheat on me.
I can't cheat on you
even if she's not with me.
I'm not good at dating.
Remember the plan to visit your house
on the weekend?
That's right.
I had all the furniture delivered.
Did you?
You needn't have done that.
I did it because I wanted to.
I will give your parents a good impression
by arranging the house before they come.
Why don't we go with...
Eun Seo and Tae Seok?
Do you want Eun Seo to come with us?
She probably hung out in that house often
when she was young.
- What's wrong?
- What?
Nothing.
I don't think Eun Seo
wants to go to the house.
Let's go, just the two of us.
Or we can go with Tae Seok.
Go in.
I don't want to.
Can you be with me a little longer?
Is Eun Seo waiting for you?
I guess it's dangerous to be there alone.
I think I must say "Good night" at least.
Are you going back
just to say "Good night?"
Okay, fine.
Good night.
Jun Seo.
Did you run?
What?
Yes.
Why? Did something happen?
What?
No.
Good night.
I wanted to say that.
Jun Seo.
I am so happy...
that I can say "Good night" to you.
Good night.
I may not have much authority,
but do I need to report to you...
when I fire someone?
We have a labor union,
and people can see things.
The act of firing Manager Kim
to reinstate Choi Eun Seo...
Are you saying I can't do that?
Do not provoke me too much.
I have an idea.
If you really dislike Manager Kim,
we can transfer her to another department.
I don't care, all I want is
not to see her again.
I will take care of it.
Do you have any other concerns?
No.
Okay.
- Wait.
- Yes?
You should say "Ms."
Pardon me?
Choi Eun Seo.
You should call her Ms. Choi Eun Seo.
I will.
Is that real? Really?
Of course.
So, come to work.
How did you convince my manager?
Well...
Did you ask her a favor?
You said you wanted your job back.
Did you ask her? Really?
Will you come back?
Thank you.
This is great.
Yes.
Can I start working tomorrow?
Yes, of course you can.
I have been worried so much.
I feel relieved.
If you want to thank me,
let's have a meal.
What do you say?
All right, why not?
Why not?
I could be your brother,
since I am a friend of your brother.
Don't smile at just anybody.
Jun Seo.
I told you that the one who comes first
is the winner.
Hello.
What was going on earlier?
I also don't see Manager Kim.
Didn't you know?
She transferred to the pool.
The pool?
The External Development Department?
That means this.
Why?
I don't know.
People say the new director dislikes her.
Poor her. How could the director do that?
It all worked out for you.
You wouldn't have been reinstated
if Manager Kim hadn't been fired.
So, stay low, and be thankful
for what you have now.
That's why things were weird earlier.
Rumor has it that there's something
going on between you and the director.
What?
I know it's nonsense.
How would you even know him?
Isn't it funny?
Who is he?
He is the youngest son of the CEO.
He caused so much trouble in Seoul,
and got transferred here.
It is an open secret.
Is that so?
I wouldn't know him, would I?
Of course not.
What was his name? Han Tae Seok?
What? Han Tae Seok?
Choi Eun Seo.
You came to work.
I have been looking all over for you.
Choi Eun Seo.
Let me go.
What is wrong?
What is the matter if I'm the director?
I'm doing nothing but hanging around,
although I'm the director. You know that.
I thought for a moment that
you might be a good person.
I thought you sincerely apologized
and asked her a favor.
I thought that's how I got my job back.
Who says I didn't apologize?
Who says that?
Would things be different if you know who?
Are you going to fire them, too?
Did the manager say that?
I will not let her...
I know people like you so well.
You care so much when you are hurt,
but you stomp on someone's life
without hesitation.
You disgust me.
You are right.
I am that kind of a person.
I don't care about others at all.
Why would it matter if I stomp on those
who bother me?
What is wrong with that?
I like you.
Yes, I like you.
I did that because I like you.
Are you happy now?
Jun Seo, where do you want this?
It can go there. Give it to me.
Get on. I'll give you a ride.
You had better get on unless you want
to make a scene here again.
- What I said.
- I know.
I know you said that
due to losing your temper.
I will not say anything to my brother.
Don't worry.
What are you doing?
Let's go tell him.
Tell your brother that I like you.
Then you will believe me.
- Look.
- Fasten your seatbelt. We'll go far.
Is it your hometown, too?
What are you looking at?
Haven't you been here often?
It's not that far.
I haven't.
This is great. It is so clean.
Is it not your first time here?
Jun Seo was here until middle school
before he went to the U.S.
He always talked about this house
while he was in the U.S.
So, I feel like I have lived in the house.
Where are they? Are they upstairs?
My dearest wife.
Happy birthday.
Her breasts? Let me see.
No. I don't want that.
- What do you want to see?
- Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
- Mom, stop him.
- Come here and sit.
Sit here and stop making a fuss.
Mom, the one I love the most. Bye.
And,
Jun Seo, goodbye.
They're not upstairs.
- Han Tae Seok, When did you come?
- Hi.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
- Eun Seo.
- Choi Eun Seo.
I think it is because of me.
I told her I like her.
(Yoon Eun Seo's Room)
I should cry again.
Isn't that what you thought?
Nothing has changed.
She is crying like a fool.
Isn't that what you thought?
She must be speaking casually now.
Finally, she is like Eun Seo.
Isn't that what you thought?
Are you Eun Seo?
Yes, I am. Jun Seo.
Jun Seo.
I think you were very close to Jun Seo.
Yes.
How did you meet him?
We studied art in New York.
I was a friend of Tae Seok.
I met Jun Seo as a friend
through Tae Seok.
It was interesting when we first met.
He didn't talk to me at all during dinner.
So I figured he wasn't
interested in me at all.
After dinner, he asked me...
what I wanted to be
if I were to be born again.
So, what did you say?
Tree. I said tree.
I...
I will be a tree.
A tree?
Yes, a tree.
Once it has taken root,
it can't move anywhere else.
I want to be such a tree.
That was our first time.
What?
I told her I like her.
I told her I mean it.
Tae Seok.
I don't like being serious,
but this is genuine.
I like Eun Seo a lot.
What did she say?
She didn't say anything.
But you will see.
I will let her know I am the only man
who can make her happy.
What do you think?
Am I good enough to go out with Eun Seo?
If I were to say no,
will you not go out with her?
I will still go out with her.
I'm not telling you this
to ask for your permission.
But, as my best friend and her cousin,
will you be happy for us?
Who made it?
- Did you cook?
- Yu Mi did.
- Is it good?
- It is tasty.
Why don't we spend the night here?
I would like that.
How about you, Eun Seo?
Is that okay with you?
By the way, on which side are you cousins?
On your father's side
or your mother's side?
Why are you so curious about that?
Since your names are Eun Seo and Jun Seo,
I guess you're paternal cousins.
Yes. What did you talk about earlier?
We talked about when we first met.
I see.
"If I were to be born again,
I would want to be a tree."
What do you want to be, Eun Seo?
I want to be Jun Seo's sister.
That is quite something.
Good for you, Yoon Jun Seo.
Choi Eun Seo.
Do you want to know how to catch a fish?
I need to clean up with them.
They will do it. Yu Mi.
Please take care of this.
Do you see this line? When you untie it,
the fishing line comes out.
If you do it this way,
the fish line stays.
And...
That is not how you do it.
You do it this way...
and turn it this way.
That is correct.
I'm not familiar with this
since it is a new product.
Are you cold?
- No, I am fine.
- It is all right.
It is hot.
They look great together.
Don't you think so, Jun Seo?
It is good to have Jun Seo's clothes.
Why are you alone?
Well.
Jun Seo went for a walk.
Do you know where Eun Seo is?
I don't know.
You cried so much here.
Did I?
Whenever you disappeared,
you were always here crying.
Did I?
You did.
We passed by this street
on a bike every day.
We stopped here when
we were stuck in the rain.
Did we?
Don't you remember it?
Do you remember me?
I don't remember that much.
Everything is a blur.
I have tried so hard to forget.
When I thought of those times,
there were many happy moments.
But I'm not happy now.
That makes me jealous.
I decided to forget it all
because I was envious of the old times.
I really did forget everything.
Didn't I?
Jun Seo.
To tell you the truth...
It has been so hard for me.
I didn't even want to recall
those good memories with you and Mom,
that's how hard it has been.
It was hard.
It has been a long time,
but can I give you a piggyback?
- Come on.
- No, Jun Seo.
Come on. Get on while I'm being nice.
Get on my back.
You are keeping me waiting forever.
What are you doing?
Why aren't they coming back yet?
Jun Seo is fine,
but I'm worried about Eun Seo.
I know.
Are you Eun Seo?
Are you?
Yu Mi. Tae Seok.
Yoon Sin Ae.
- Sin Ae.
- I missed you.
Why didn't you call us?
You haven't changed.
Am I not heavy?
No.
I think I'm heavy.
Am I the third one now?
Besides Mom, Yu Mi, Sin Ae.
Is it me after that?
You're not the third one.
Am I not even the third? You are mean.
What about you?
Where am I on your list?
You know where you are.
Do I?
You are on the top, of course.
Let me get off. You must be tired.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean by his cousin?
Who is his cousin?
I'm sorry for being late...
Jun Seo.
I can't live without you now. Come to me.
I need to talk to you, Yu Mi.
Don't you love me?
I thought I could try to.
Eun Seo, please help me out.
I am nothing without Jun Seo.
Let me have you, too.
You can trust me.
Let's forget that we even met.
Only then can we all be happy.
Don't leave.
I won't let you leave.